lookagain.co.uk 2012-01-21

# What is your privacy policy? - LookAgain Help

  * Help
  * Privacy

We respect your privacy, and promise to use any information we hold about you in a safe and responsible way. By shopping with us, you are agreeing to our Privacy Policy, in particular, our use of your information, as outlined below. We control information we have collected about you that is relevant to your account. This includes: 

  * Your credit history 
  * The credit histories of any people you are financially linked to 
  * Your purchasing habits with us 
  * To verify your identity and that you are least 18 years of age (we cannot sell any goods to you if you are below 18 years of age.

We will use your information in the following ways: 

  * **Reference checks**  
When you open an account with us we will need to check your credit history and store the search on file. We will re-run checks each time you apply for, or we offer you further credit. 
  * **Marketing  
**We may contact you with promotions we think might interest you, as part of our market research, either by mail, telephone or email. 
  * **Third Party Marketing**  
We may share your details to third parties whose offers we think might interest you. 
  * **Training  
**We randomly monitor calls made to our Customer Services for training. 

We may also pass information about you to agents, service providers and employees to carry out services. In the course of providing such services, we may transfer your personal information outside the European Economic Area. We will employ appropriate security measures to protect your personal information where this is the case.

This information will not be used for any other purpose. If you do not want us to use your information for third party marketing purposes, please write to us at:  
Look Again  
Ingleby Road  
Bradford  
BD99 2XG 

Any information we collect about customers’ browsing and buying habits is used to improve the Look Again website and the products and services offered to our customers. It also assists us with the detection and prevention of fraud. 

We will collect information from you when opening your account and processing your orders. 

We will automatically collect information such as your browser IP address to make shopping with us easier, for example, remembering your log-in details. 

We will use cookies (electronic tags) to monitor your browsing and buying habits on our site, for example, which pages are visited, and whether they are purchased from. 

Information we hold about you is securely stored electronically. When you open an account with us, your details are encrypted, and remain so every time you purchase from us. Personal information is encrypted to protect against fraud. 

Callers to our Customer Services will be subject to a security check Online customers will require a log-in and password to access their account. 

Our courier service will have selected access to your details for delivery purposes only.
